Okay. That's okay.
Get that.
Hey.
[WALT PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
[JESSE COUGHING]
WALT: Oh, God. Please.
JESSE: Oh, jeez.
WALT:
Please.
[BRAKES SQUEALING]
It's a bold plan, Mr. White.
You sure this
is the way to go?
Yeah.
WALT:
Gracias.
[MOANS]
[BOB JAMES' "FEEL LIKE
MAKING LOVE" PLAYlNG OVER PA]
MAN:
You see that?
[PEOPLE CHATTERlNG]
[♪♪♪]
SKYLER: What does he remember?
MAN: Not a whole lot.
He came in dehydrated
and disoriented,
but once we gave him fluids
he stabilized pretty quickly.
SKYLER:
But I mean...
He knows where he is?
MAN: Oh, yes, yes. Absolutely.
It's only the last day or so
that seem to be missing.
Go on in.
He's probably awake.
Oh.
My God.
Oh, Walter.
[BOTH SOBBlNG]
WALTER:
I'm so sorry.
Come here.
You know who
I am, right?
Yes, son.
I know who you are.
Come here.
Give your old man a hug.
It's so good to see you.
How do you feel?
Better.
Yeah. l...
I feel like myself.
Really, l mean, in...
[SIGHS]
The past couple days are missing,
but other than that,
I feel fine.
My God, Walt.
What a day this
has been, huh?
So, Uncle Hank,
he was in a shootout?
A shootout?
He killed some guy.
Some big drug dealer.
Uncle Hank
wasted him.
Oh, my God.
Is he all right?
SKYLER:
Absolutely fine.
Where did this happen?
How could he--?
Walt, everything's okay.
We' re all okay.
We' ll be all right.
MARIE [OVER PHONE]:
And no idea what caused it?
No.
But they're gonna run
a whole series of tests, so...
But what could it be?
I mean, did they give you
a worst-case scenario?
Um, I really...
You know, there's no point
in getting ahead of ourselves, so...
Well, which supermarket?
Is it, like, a big one?
Like, a chain?
Marie.
I-- Don't get me wrong.
I think it's just great that, you know,
he's back and he' s feeling better.
I just-- l mean...
He-- Naked?
He was naked.
Naked.
In a supermarket.
It wasn't Whole Foods, was it?
[SIGHS]
In any case, l'm gonna get
over there as soon as l can.
No, no. Don't worry about it
right now, Marie.
How's Hank?
You know, I ran over here
and l got to see him all of
30 seconds before
they yanked him away.
You know, you' d think
today of all days
they' d let him
go home on time.
But how is he? Really?
Hank?
He's indestructible,
you know that.
I identified myself and told
the suspect to show his hands,
turn and face me.
At this point, I identified
the suspect as Mr. Salamanca
and observed what
appeared to be a gunshot
wound in his midsection.
He was shot previous
to your arrival?
Yes, sir.
Again I instructed him
to show his hands.
Mr. Salamanca lunged
toward the vehicle
and fired on me with
what I ascertained to be
an M1 6 assault rifle.
I returned fire
and sought cover
as Mr. Salamanca proceeded
to engage me.
When he paused to reload,
I was able to take
an effective shot.
Agent Schrader, what were
you doing in a shooting fight
on your own, with no backup?
Mr. Salamanca' s presence
was not something I'd anticipated.
I was tending to another matter.
What other matter?
An unrelated family matter.
Searching for your brother-in-law,
as l understand.
Your brother-in-law?
Yes, sir. He's since been found.
He's fine. The whole thing
was a misunderstanding.
But at the time, he'd been
missing for several hours,
and since he's in poor health,
the whole family was concerned.
I was talking to his friends
and acquaintances,
trying to get a fix
on his whereabouts.
The Monte Carlo at the scene
belonged to a former student of his,
a Jesse Pinkman.
I was tracking down
Mr. Pinkman's car when I
came across Mr. Salamanca.
And what about this Pinkman?
What was his car doing at the
crime scene?
Have you run him down yet?
Not yet, but we're working on it.
[INDlSTlNCT RADlO CHATTER]
BADGER:
Man, they're like
Jehovah' s Witnesses.
They don't give up.
I don't get it.
Why don' t they just
kick your door down?
They need probable cause.
Probable cause?
Yo, what did you do?
Rob a bank?
I told you,
this is serious shit.
I'm like an outlaw.
Okay.
[CAR DRIVES AWAY]
Let's do this.
Holy Christ!
You' re Willy Wonka.
You are Willy Wonka,
and l got the golden ticket.
Oh! Put me on your
magical boat, man.
Sail me down your
chocolaty river of meth.
So where you keep
the pseudo?
It's a P2P cook. That barrel?
Aqueous methylamine.
With that, you don't need pseudo.
Come on, help me out, man.
No pseudo?
Come to me, beautiful baby.
I'm gonna be so good to you.
Oh, my God.
Just take this, here.
But I can't just let you
break this down.
I mean, that'd be sacrilege.
I told you, that's why we're here.
You saw the cops. Right?
Sure.
But couldn't we just
cook one quick batch?
You know, for the road?
No, forget it, all right?
This stuff has to go, like, now.
Dude, you owe me.
I mean, we're cool and all,
but I ain't forgetting you just
left me stranded.
God, Badger!
Don't mess with me.
Got it?
Yeah, l got it.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
JESSE:
Oh, my God.
[BOTH PANTING]
Okay, that's all of it.
This was a bad choice.
[MOTOR WHIRRING]
You sure about this guy?
BADGER:
He's totally, totally cool.
He's my cousin.
Yo, what'd we say, 500?
We didn't say, and it's 1 000.
Thousand bucks?
Come on, where you
towing it, man, Seattle?
It ain' t the miles,
it' s the cargo.
Look, l mean,
all I got on me is...
[JESSE SIGHS]
560.
You know what?
JESSE: Hey-- No--
Clovis, he'll pay you
the rest later.
He's totally good for it.
Jesse's a stand-up dude.
That right?
You a stand-up dude?
Yeah, l am.
I will get you the other 500.
Five hundred more.
Your word' s
your bond, right?
Right.
I saved your
skinny ass, yo.
I totally vouched
for you.
What are you
doing now, exactly?
I'm giving you like
two hours,
and then l'm calling on
a pay phone, not a cell phone.
You' re not using your own name.
I mean, obviously.
Look, dude, I'll do, like,
what you said, but why?
Why do you gotta
go and do this?
They need probable cause.
I'm giving it to them.
What's the last thing
you remember?
Uh, well, l was driving home.
I think.
And...
SKYLER:
Do you remember
coming home?
You came in, and I asked
why you were out of breath?
You don't remember talking to me
when l was in the bathtub?
No, I'm sorry, l don' t.
Nothing else?
No fleeting images?
Uh, well, no. l, um...
I was--
I was walking down
some road or highway
with a lot of headlights,
and l remember feeling fear.
Oh. That' s it.
All right. Thank you.
Well, there's definitely
some good news here.
The MRl shows no metastases.
Meaning the cancer
hasn't spread to the brain?
Yeah, we're looking
really good.
Oh, thank God.
So, what was it, then?
SOPER:
Well, there's no sign
of stroke or seizure.
And considering your condition,
the blood panel looks good.
Then what are we talking about?
What happened?
As of right now, we really
can' t say.
Forgive me.
Granted, this is not my field,
but isn' t it possible
that this had something to do
with all the prescriptions
I've been taking?
There's the antiemetic,
the antitussive,
the this, the that.
Not to mention the chemo itself.
Ahem. And being off all of them
for the past few days, I have to say
I'm feeling much better.
Yeah, and, you know,
when we pick up these
medications,
the information sheets
are as long as your arm.
I mean, it's page after page
of side effects and warnings.
Right, exactly.
Could it be that simple?
Well, we' ll take
another look at that, sure.
Walt, I understand that you've been
kind of stressed out lately.
Stressed out? I--
No, I don't think l'm--
SKYLER: Walt, please.
Stressed out
is putting it mildly.
Well, l guess I've had a lot
on my mind lately, but as I've said,
I'm feeling much better.
Shouldn't we be talking about
when l can get out of here?
Well, that may still be
a ways down the road.
A ways down the road?
Actually, I think our next move is
to schedule a psychiatric evaluation.
Now, is that absolutely
necessary?
Walt, nobody likes being
in the hospital. l get that.
But until we know
what caused this incident,
we can' t be certain
it won't recur.
[TOlLET FLUSHES]
That your last hit?
Yeah.
JESSE:
All right, finish it quick.
[♪♪♪]
[CAN OPENS]
[WENDY SCREAMS]
AGENT: Show your hands.
Get on your stomach now.
Get on your stomach now!
Get over. Roll! Do it now!
[WENDY GASPING]
[GRUNTlNG]
JESSE:
I'm going, I' m going.
Hey, what's going on, huh?
What did I do?
Jesse Pinkman, I presume.
[HANDS DRUMMING]
What, man?
HANK: Tell me again.
Again?
What's there to tell, okay?
Her and I were partying, that's it.
Since Saturday night?
Partying for three days
straight, huh?
Just bumping uglies
and smoking that crystal
you got from your pal, Tuco?
Taco? l don' t know any Taco,
and l damn sure didn't say
anything about no crystal.
Three days,
you must have got hungry.
Uh, yeah, l guess.
HANK: You order take-out?
Yeah.
Yeah, where from?
You get yourself a little
of that moo goo gai pan
from that chink place
around the corner?
No, no, we didn't. We got stuff
from the vending machine.
You know, Funyuns.
I had a Hot Pocket.
Funyuns and Hot Pockets?
You didn't notice your car
was gone?
No, not until you guys went
and busted down the door.
Okay, now, who's gonna
pay for that, huh?
Management's gonna
be on my ass for sure.
How come you weren't
answering your cell phone?
It was in my car.
That right?
Yeah.
We found your car,
but your phone wasn' t in it.
Wait, you found my car?
You found my car?
Awesome.
DEA all the way. Yes.
Since we're talking
about missing property,
did you, um...?
Did you leave anything else
in the car?
Like what?
Like what? Like, uh...
I don't know. Like this?
[SNIFFS]
Sixty-seven thousand,
nine hundred and 20 dollars.
Ah, that's not mine.
HANK:
That's not yours? Huh.
He says it's not his, Gomie.
GOMEZ: Hmm.
HANK:
Gee, I really thought
this might be yours.
I wish.
Unclaimed drug money,
huh? Nice.
You know what we got here,
Gomie, don' t you?
That's a new interdiction van
right there, yeah.
Definitely some new
softball jerseys, because
we need them, you know?
Good thing Tuco's already dead.
I lost this kind of money,
I'd wanna kill myself.
So who' s your chief,
little lnjun?
What?
What does that even mean?
It means l think your story's bullshit.
I think you know
who Tuco Salamanca was.
I think your car was there
because you were there.
Tuco had a bullet in him
when l got there and I think you
know something about that too.
So, what are you
saying?
I shot someone?
With, like, a gun?
You?
No.
Only shooting you do
is into a Kleenex.
But I think you know
the badass who did.
Look, l was partying
with Wendy, okay?
Funyuns and boom-boom.
No.
I don't think so.
Tell you what.
We' re gonna, um,
go talk to that skinny yeast factory
of a girlfriend you got.
And you know what?
I got a feeling she's gonna,
you know, roll on you.
Don't go nowhere.
Ah.
Oops.
Where's my root beer?
Come on. l gotta pee,
and l got low blood sugar.
I got medical issues.
Medical issues?
Like, what kind
of medical issues?
You got penis withdrawal?
You got schlongus
interruptus?
Wendy, listen.
Talk to me
and you get a root beer
and a tinkle.
Now, tell me the last three days.
I told you,
we were shacked up
since Saturday.
Neither of you left the room?
Not even for a little, little minute?
Not even for a second?
For a second?
I don't know, maybe.
Maybe?
Did Jesse leave the room?
He did, didn't he?
Wendy, you can do it.
You can do it, Wendy.
Wendy, Wendy, Wendy.
You know you wanna go back
to giving windys, Wendy.
It's you. l know you.
You' re the one in the black truck.
You wanted me to do that kid.
GOMEZ: What?
The kid with the crutches.
The football player.
How about we stay on topic?
Look, Jesse came over to the palace
at 1 1 :00 Saturday night.
We were together the whole time,
and he never left the room.
And that' s all
I'm saying about that.
Now, come on.
Where's my root beer?
GOMEZ: You wanted her
to bang a football player,
you big, bald pervert?
It's a long story, Gomie.
Yeah, l'm sure it is,
and l wanna hear it,
but first we gotta kick
Pinkman loose.
Not yet. I got one more shot
at that little skid mark.
CHAVEZ:
And how are you sleeping?
Um, fine. Most nights.
Yeah, good.
Have you noticed any
recurring thoughts or images,
things you can't
get out of your head?
[SIGHS]
How about feelings of guilt
or persecution?
No. Look, doctor,
I don't mean to be rude,
but where is this going,
exactly?
We' re starting a process, Walt.
An ongoing process.
Do you prefer Walt or Walter?
Ongoing for how long?
I just met you.
It's hard to say.
We could be talking about days,
weeks, months.
Look, doctor, l feel fine, really.
Now, if this is truly necessary,
can' t I continue
as an outpatient?
Walt,
a fugue state
is a very serious event.
What if you were to disassociate
while you were driving?
What if you were
to get into a situation
where you could be shot
by the police?
You understand,
we can' t allow you to leave
until we're certain
what happened was
a non-recurring event.
Saying you feel fine
doesn't solve this.
Would you tell me about
patient confidentiality?
It's very straightforward.
Without your permission,
I can't disclose anything
you tell me to anyone.
What about my family?
Not your family,
not to the police.
Not to anyone.
The only exception would be
if you threatened to kill someone.
Then I'd be able to tell that person,
but only that person.
And you,
as a medical practitioner,
you abide by these
strictures absolutely.
Yes.
All right.
There was no fugue state.
I remember everything.
The truth is,
I couldn't stand to spend
another second in that house.
I just had to get out,
and so I left.
I didn't think about it.
I just did it.
I walked for a long time,
and when I couldn't walk
anymore, l hitchhiked.
I got as far as Gallup...
and then it was just time
to come home.
So...
being found naked
in a supermarket,
that was your way of
giving credibility to a lie?
Of avoiding questions
about your disappearance?
Why run away?
What did you feel
you had to run from?
Doctor, my wife
is seven months pregnant
with a baby we didn't intend.
My 1 5-year-old son
has cerebral palsy.
I am an extremely overqualified
high school chemistry teacher.
When I can work,
I make $43,700 per year.
I have watched
all of my colleagues
and friends surpass me
in every way imaginable,
and within 1 8 months,
I will be dead.
And you ask why l ran?
[BELL DINGS]
HANK:
Gomie, you wanna do the honors?
[GOMEZ SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[BELL DINGS]
What's that mean?
That means yes.
Yes is a bell,
no is no bell.
Oh, come on, this is bullshit.
I mean, look at this dude, all right?
He doesn't even know what planet
he's living on.
Señor, are we on
the planet Mars?
Are we on the
planet Saturn?
Are we on the planet Earth?
[JESSE SCOFFS]
Señor, is today Friday?
Is today Monday?
Is today Tuesday?
Okay, seems like he' s all there.
Let's go for it.
Señor,
was this man at your
house yesterday?
Señor, was this man
at your house yesterday?
This guy right here,
he was at your house, right?
Was he doing business
with your nephew Tuco?
Señor, are you scared
of this man?
No, he's not scared.
Come on, Granddad.
Don't you wanna
help us out?
[DEFECATES]
[GRUNTS]
Oh, man.
I guess that's a no.
GOMEZ:
I told you, numbnuts.
This guy's OG.
HANK:
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Kept his mouth shut for
1 7 years in San Quentin.
Stroke or no stroke,
old-school gangbang
Mexicans don't help the feds.
HANK: All right already.
It was worth a try at least.
GOMEZ:
We gotta kick Pinkman loose.
It's all right.
He's nobody anyway.
What, you telling me
you buy that lame-ass
story of his?
I buy that lame-ass story
more than I buy he had
anything to do
with shooting Tuco, man.
JESSE:
Dad? Hey, Dad.
Hey, can you hear me?
Uh, yeah, yeah, no,
I'm fine. Hey, l'm, uh...
What's--?
She did? No, I didn't
get any messages.
You know, I actually
lost my phone, and I've been
too busy to get a new one.
I've been busy as--
As totally productive.
Hey, you know what?
I'm actually zeroing in
on a job.
Yeah, yeah, data entry,
like we talked about.
Yeah, l'm totally amped.
Hey, could you give me a ride?
I'm actually-- I'm downtown
and my car's in the, uh...
Oh, no. Yeah, hey,
that's cool. I will--
I'll call you later
when you have some...
Okay. Yeah. No. I, uh--
I get it. I get it.
Okay, bye.
Thanks.
So, what are you doing now?
Waffle House?
Waffle House is good.
[PHONE RINGING]
Pay phone?
Pay phone, in the middle
of nowhere, nobody followed.
So how did it go?
[SIGHS]
Okay. You?
They sweated me plenty,
but they finally cut me loose.
So you getting out of there?
Tomorrow.
So who came for you?
The DEA?
What did they ask you?
Yeah, that's the thing, you know.
Your scumbag brother-in-law
took my rainy-day fund.
Your what? What is that?
My rainy-day fund.
Sixty-eight thousand, okay?
Cue-ball son of a bitch
laughed in my face.
Now I got like 80 bucks
to my name.
Wait, wait.
What does he know?
Does he know
it' s your money?
No, man.
He doesn't know shit, okay?
The plan worked.
They bought it.
I got bills due, man.
I'm screwed.
Did he mention my name?
No. Thanks for caring.
What about the basement?
It's clean.
And the RV?
Badger's cousin took it
to his garage. It' s safe.
Can he get it running again?
Why?
So we can cook.
So you still wanna cook?
Seriously?
What's changed, Jesse?
[HANGS UP RECEIVER]
WALT: Seven-hundred
thirty-seven thousand.
Twenty-one pounds,
minus cash on hand...
Cash on hand.
[COUGHlNG]
[MOBlLE CHlMES]
[CHIMES]
[CRUTCHES CLlNKlNG]
[GASPS]
Sorry, honey. Did I wake you?
No, I was awake.
Want some cornflakes?
Uh, yeah, sure.
You okay?
Yeah.
[THE BE GOOD TANYAS' "WAITING
AROUND TO DlE" PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Southwest Aniline again?
What's this?
It's the blue meth we found
up by your late homey.
Tuco wasn't my homey, any more
than Charlie Manson was yours.
Lab says it got cooked,
P2P-style.
P2P, huh?
So, what are you thinking?
The two stooges over here
cooked it?
Lab said that blue meth's
the purest they' ve seen.
At least since this.
Krazy-8.
Yeah.
Krazy-8, Tuco...
Somehow, some way,
it' s all connected.
A simple explanation,
only l'm not seeing it,
and it's making my head hurt.
That's because you're working
that ugly melon too hard.
It's dead around here.
Let's go get a couple of beers.
It's 1 1 in the morning.
I'm buying.
You' re buying? Holy crap.
What, is it
Cinco de Mayo already?
Oh, yeah.
ALL:
Surprise!
Aw, you little
sneaky bastard, you.
Very nice work.
Thank you, sir.
What's this?
MAN 1 : Look what we got you.
Ahh! Look at that,
I love it.
They got the gut right.
Hey.
MAN 2: There you go.
Hey, thanks, man.
Thank you.
We all got you a little something,
and this is from all of us.
Ah, you shouldn't have.
Oh, you sick, sick puppies.
I love it. Oh!
You going to finish
your apple juice?
Uh, no, thanks, buddy.
You take it.
You' re supposed
to drink it.
The nurse said you
have to stay hydrated.
But I'm not thirsty.
Dad. Drink it.
[KNOCKlNG ON DOOR]
Hey. Hey.
Better late than
never, huh?
Hey.
How you doing, buddy?
You all right?
I see the mark of
the beast there, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Marie stopped by this morning.
They really cheer the place up.
Oh, hey, I ran into
Sky downstairs.
They' re rounding up
a wheelchair for you,
you freeloading bastard.
WALT JR.:
So tell us about the shootout.
Ah, I was, you know,
just doing my job.
Whole thing was over
in about five seconds.
Say, Walt, you know,
how are you?
I'm okay.
Really, l'm feeling fine.
Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah.
The doctor is calling it a...
An isolated episode of
transient global amnesia.
Damn.
Which means
non-recurring.
Non-- Well, non-recurring.
That sounds good, yeah.
Sounds real good, huh?
I'll tell you what,
I'm glad you' re back.
You know, you really
gave us a scare.
Listen, Hank.
I don't know what
to say. l mean,
you going out there
looking for me put you
in danger, and l'm so--
Sorry, sorry doesn't
even cut it. Not nearly.
No, no, no. Is that what
you' re worried about?
Forget it. No, no, no.
Look, the office,
they' re treating me like
I'm Eliot Ness, okay?
I mean, they threw me
a party, the gals baked me
a chocolate-chip cake
like you wouldn' t
believe, okay?
Hey, you ought to
disappear more often.
[HANK LAUGHS]
Just kidding.
Don't do that.
Uh... Oh, hey, look.
Look what they gave me.
Look what
they gave me.
WALT JR.:
What is it?
Ha-ha-ha. That, gentlemen,
is the grill of the guy I shot.
His grill?
Yeah.
It kind of goes over
the front teeth like that,
you know?
Sort of a fashion
statement, l guess.
You know, certain folks
are attracted to shiny things.
Wow, cool.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
I can't tell you how good
it feels to be home.
I'll get these in the wash.
Okay.
Um...
Say, honey, l...
I was just thinking about
going out to 7-Eleven.
Do you need anything?
Big Gulp? Slim Jim?
Skyler, listen to me.
This will not happen
again, okay?
I won't let it.
I'm still here. I'm me,
and we're gonna be okay.
Walt...
do you have a second
cell phone?
A second cell phone?
The night you disappeared,
you came in when I was
taking a bath
and you were very upset.
It was like something
terrible had happened.
And then your
cell phone rang.
I saw you check the number,
and then you got up
and just disappeared.
Hm.
Yeah.
And when Hank
checked your phone records,
there was no call.
No call on the phone
I know about.
Wow.
That is odd.
I mean, I don't remember
any of that,
but one thing l am sure of is that
I don't have a second cell phone.
Okay.
[♪♪♪]